Christopher Kelly

905-995-1105 ckelly.tor@gmail.com • www.chriskelly48th.ca Toronto, Ontario, M5R 1E9

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

5+ years of experience with front-end (Angular.js) and back-end (Node.js) web development as well as mobile app development (Java/Kotlin). Experience in database management leveraging Oracle DB and MySQL. Used to fast-paced work environments and focused on meeting deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Technical Support

2020-Present

Crossover • Remote Contractor

Supported businesses globally with a wide array of B2B products and technologies in a remote environment using Zendesk and Jira

- Leveraged technical experience in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to diagnose and solve customer issues
- Simultaneously supported a variety of SaaS products including BiznessApps for app resellers, and Olive for print media owners
- Drew heavily on work ethic and time management skills to excel in a fully remote workplace
- Contributed to and expertly utilized company knowledgebase to provide customers with quick and accurate support

Ignite TV Technical Support

2018 - 2019

Rogers Communications • Toronto, Ontario

Supported the initial product release and roll out of IPTV with Rogers by providing front-line technical support to customers

- Leveraged diagnostic tools to determine and resolve technical issues for Ignite TV customers
- Experienced in supporting both cable and internet products
- · Cross-trained to provide basic customer service and sales solutions

Retail Manager

2013 - 2018

Best Buy • Ajax, Ontario

Responsible for merchandising and inventory management (Product Process Senior) / Responsible for training and increasing revenue in each department (Sales Senior)

- Increased productivity by providing weekly reports to management
- · Recognized in company memo for providing exceptional customer service
- Chosen to help open a new store and train all new staff members (Oshawa)

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer

SKILLS

- Object Oriented Programming using Java, Kotlin, C# and C++ 5 Years
- Front-End Web Development using HTML/CSS/JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS 5 years
- Back-End Web Development using NodeJS and Express 3 years
- · Cross-Platform App development using Ionic and Xamarin Forms 3 years
- · Native App Development using Android Studio 3 years
- Database experience using NoSQL tools like MongoDB and MySQL tools like DB2 and Oracle - 2 years

PROFESSIONAL CREDENTIALS

- Udemy C++ using Unreal
- · Canadian Red Cross First-Aid Certificate

LINKS

- www.chriskelly48th.ca Personal Website with links and descriptions of work
- github.com/ckelly2112 Personal GitHub Page
- · linkedin.com/in/ckellytor LinkedIn Page

References

Adeel Vanthaliwala, Senior Product Manager, Sportsnet, DTC Platform and NHL Live T: 647-262-6877 E: moadeel@gmail.com

Further references available upon request.